Guide to the Time Inc. Magazine Development Group Records 1967-1987, 2003 MS 3009-RG 40
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.A.5. Art Department: Graphic Development Files, 1985-1986; 3.75 Linear feet in 1 record carton and 3 flat boxes
  The Graphic Development files include drafts of designs for magazines under development. The majority of files are from designing Picture week. Records include designs for mastheads, covers, logos, table of contents, and page layouts. Picture Week covers and logos files shows early attempts for "Picture News" and includes several more logo designs than are used in the dummies. Boxes 3751, 3762, and 3763 have larger format materials.
  Organizedl alphabetically.
  - Express: Logos, undated (Offsite-box 3749, Folder 1)
  - Flash: Logos, undated (Offsite-box 3749, Folder 2)
  - Picture Week: General, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3763, Folder 1)
  - Picture Week: Covers, 1986 (Offsite-box 3749, Folder 3-5)
  - Picture Week: Covers, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3762)
  - Picture Week: Covers and Logos, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3749, Folder 6-8)
  - Picture Week: Logos, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3763, Folder 2-3)
  - Picture Week: Masthead, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3763, Folder 4)
  - Picture Week: Page Layouts, 1986 (Offsite-box 3763, Folder 5-8)
  - Together and Unidentified, undated (Offsite-box 3751)
- Series II.B.1. 1981-1986 Business and Publishing: Publisher Bruce Barnet Files, 1983-1987; 0.66 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  Bruce Barnet joined MDG as Publisher, reporting to VP of Magazines Kelso Sutton, in December 1983. Prior he held positions as the final Circulation Director of Life, senior vice president of Time-Life Films, and Fortune Assistant Publisher. When teh MDG closed, he took over as Publisher of Discover to administrate its sale, then was named Vice President of Planning for the Magazine Group.
  Bruce Barnet's files document the business decisions of the later Magazine Development Group.
  - Picture Week: Board Meeting, 1986 September 18 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 1)
  - Picture Week: Presentation, 1986 March 13 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 2)
  - Picture Week: Presentation, 1986 May 9 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 3)
  - Picture Week: Sutton/Grunwald Meeting, 1986 May 1 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 4)
  - Picture Week: Test Market Fact Book, 1986 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 5)
  - Skunkworks Presentation, 1985 April 30 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 6)
  - Skunkworks Proposals, 1984 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 7)
  - Trade Magazine Group Analysis, 1984 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 8)
  - Trade Publishing, 1984 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 9-10)
  - Two Existing Opportunities: Best of Business and Ziff Davis, 1983 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 11)
- Series II.B.2. 1981-1986 Business and Publishing: Associate Publisher Don Spurdle Files, 1984-1986; 0.33 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  Don Spurdle's files document the business and publishing decisions of the later Magazine Development Group.
  - Development Structures, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 12-13)
  - Skunkworks: General, 1985 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 14)
  - Skunkworks: Proposals, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3752, Folder 15-17)